with high medical costs having a medical
insurance plan is an important aspect of
good financial planning for example
coronary bypass surgery costs between 25
000 ringgit to 80 000 Ringgit it is wise
to have a medical insurance plan even if
you are healthy to take care of
increasing and unexpected High medical
expenses medical insurance plan that
comes with medical card provides the
convenience of seamless admission
did you know that the premiums paid for
medical plans will form part of an
insurance claims poll that is shared
paid claims are taken from this claims
pool in view of the projected medical
inflation of 16.18 in 2022 the
hospitalization expenses are expected to
get higher and if there are a lot of
claims the claim spool will become
smaller therefore they will come to a
point where medical repricing will need
to be performed and all policy owners in
the claims pool will face increase of
premiums just as there's no claim
discount and CD for motor insurance
there are medical insurance plans that
come with this feature too this type of
plan provides protection while rewarding
you for staying healthy how does the NCD
feature in a medical insurance work upon
successful sign up you will enjoy a 30
upfront discount on your insurance
charges a perfect quick welcome gift for
you every year thereafter you can
receive up to 40 NCD when no claim is
made however if a claim is made the NCD
will reset to zero percent there may be
instances where the NCD amount is higher
than the claim amount so you may want to
enjoy the NCD instead of making small
claims if less claims are made the
claims pool will be able to last longer
and reduce the Quantum of medical
repricing most importantly in the event
of medical repricing NCD will continue
to apply on the repriced insurance
charges
find out more on medical plans with NCD
feature by visiting our website calling
our customer care line or getting in
touch with our professional advisor
today
[Music]